Some connections never die.
Mr. Harrigan's Phone is a drama, horror, mystery
film directed by John Lee Hancock.
Craig, a young boy living in a small town befriends
an older, reclusive billionaire, Mr.
The two form a bond over books and an iPhone, but when the man passes
away the boy discovers that not everything dead is gone.
Mr. Harrigan, played by Donald Sutherland.
Craig, played by Jaeden Martell.
Ms. Hart, played by Kirby Howell-Baptiste.
Craig's Dad, played by Joe Tippett.
Kenny Yankovich, played by Cyrus Arnold.
U-Boat, played by Conor William Wright.
Harrigan's Phone is a 2022 American supernatural coming-of-age
horror film written and directed by John Lee Hancock.
It is based on the novella of the same name by Stephen
King from the collection If It Bleeds.
The film stars Donald Sutherland, Jaeden Martell, Joe
Tippett, and Kirby Howell-Baptiste.
It follows Craig who has a strong friendship with retired businessman John
Harrigan; both get their first iPhones after the former wins a lottery.
Despite the latter's death, a supernatural connection persists between them
through their phones, one of which is buried alongside Harrigan.
Harrigan's Phone was released on October 5, 2022, by Netflix.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of small town, materialism,
coming of age, grief, based on short story.
The tone is dark and emotional and mind_bending.